const reactQuestions = [
  {
    question: 'Arbitrary inputs of components are called __________',
    a: 'Keys',
    b: 'Props',
    c: 'Elements',
    d: 'Ref',
    answer: 'b',
  },
  {
    question:
      '_________ can be done while more than one element needs to be returned from a component',
    a: 'Abstraction',
    b: 'Packing',
    c: 'Insulation',
    d: 'Wrapping',
    answer: 'd',
  },
  {
    question: ' Lifecycle methods are mainly used ___________',
    a: 'to keep track of event history',
    b: 'to enhance components',
    c: 'freeup resources',
    d: 'to unmount components',
    answer: 'c',
  },
  {
    question: 'In JSX most of the errors can be caught during _________',
    a: 'Interpretation',
    b: 'Execution',
    c: 'Compilation',
    d: 'Build',
    answer: 'c',
  },
  {
    question:
      'ref is used to refer a element / component returned by _______________',
    a: 'react()',
    b: 'render()',
    c: 'reduce()',
    d: 'refer()',
    answer: 'b',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following is used to capture all click events in a window?',
    a: 'window.captureEvents(Event.CLICK);',
    b: 'window.routeEvents(Event.CLICK );',
    c: 'window.handleEvents(Event.CLICK);',
    d: 'window.raiseEvents(Event.CLICK );',
    answer: 'a',
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the smallest building block of ReactJS?',
    a: 'none',
    b: 'props',
    c: 'elements',
    d: 'components',
    answer: 'c',
  },
  {
    question:
      'React keeps track of what items have changed, been added, or been removed from a list using ________.',
    a: 'state',
    b: 'props',
    c: 'ref',
    d: 'keys',
    answer: 'd',
  },
  {
    question: 'React is mainly for building _____________.',
    a: 'Database',
    b: 'Connectivity',
    c: 'User Interface',
    d: 'Design Platform',
    answer: 'c',
  },
  {
    question: 'nvoked once, only on the client, after rendering occurs.',
    a: 'ComponentWillMount',
    b: 'shouldComponentMount',
    c: 'ComponentWillUnmount',
    d: 'ComponentDidMount',
    answer: 'd',
  },
]

export default reactQuestions
